All who enter here...
ผู้ที่เข้ามายังที่แห่งนี้
...are either jailers...
ถ้าไม่ใช่ผู้คุม
...or prisoners.
ก็คือนักโทษ
Which are you?
แล้วคุณเป็นแบบไหน?
Neither. I'm merely a lost traveler.
ไม่ใช่ทั้งสองอย่าง ฉันเป็นแค่นักท่องเที่ยวที่หลงทาง
What a spectacle! The Stellaron, the Ambrosial Arbor, the Disciples of Sanctus Medicus, the Lord Ravager...
เป็นภาพที่น่าตื่นเต้นดีนะ! ทั้ง Stellaron, Ambrosial Arbor, สาวก Sanctus Medicus และลอร์ดผู้ล้างผลาญ...
...a series of threats...
ภัยคุกคามมากมายที่ถาโถมเข้ามา
...that almost succeeded in diverting attention away...
เกือบจะเบี่ยงเบนความสนใจของทุกคนได้แล้ว...
...from the crucial question...
จนลืมคำถามที่ดูเหมือนจะไม่ได้สำคัญอีกต่อไป...
They who brought the Stellaron onto the Xianzhou...
ผู้ที่นำ "Stellaron" เข้ามาใน Xianzhou...
What was their motive?
มีแผนอะไรกันแน่?
Will you surrender...
จะยอมจำนนแต่โดยดี
...or do you require encouragement...
หรือจะให้ช่วยสงเคราะห์ให้คุณไปสบายๆ
...abomination of Yaoshi.
สิ่งชั่วร้ายของ Yaoshi
General, my power does indeed stem from the Abundance.
ท่านนายพล พลังของฉันมาจาก "เฟื่องฟู" ก็จริง
But I'm the same as you.
แต่ฉันก็เหมือนกับคุณ
We are both enemies of Yaoshi.
เราต่างก็เป็นศัตรูของ Yaoshi
That's right, Jing Yuan.
ใช่แล้ว Jing Yuan
Stay out of our way.
อย่าขวางทางเรา
The revival of the Arbor is an omen. It's time for the Xianzhou to choose its next path.
การฟื้นคืนของ Ambrosial Arbor นั้นเป็นลางบอกเหตุ มันแสดงให้เห็นล่วงหน้าว่า Xianzhou ได้มาถึงช่วงเวลาที่ต้องเลือกเส้นทางแห่งโชคชะตาแล้ว
The Reignbow Arbiter, the Plagues Author, the Ruin Author...
คันศรลิขิต พินาศโรคา และพินาศมลายสูญ...
This is a chess game between Aeons. If you don't stand with the winners, you stand to lose.
นี่คือเกมเดินหมากระหว่างเทพเจ้า ถ้านายไม่ยืนอยู่ข้างฝ่ายที่ชนะ นายก็จะเป็นผู้แพ้
And this time,
แต่ในครั้งนี้
We will put the Abundance in their grave.
เราจะต้องส่ง "เฟื่องฟู" ไปสู่ความตาย